Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; Series VII; 15.62; (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings
    - Audiocassettes, commercially released and non-commercial
      - Works by others, unsorted, (34 audiocassettes)
        - Prism International, 1990; 1; 00:56:42 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506556)
          Robertson, Wes. "Stopping by the Woods on a Snowy Evening" by Robert Frost
          Bissett, Bill. "liquid dansrs"
          Bissett, Bill. "caribu rd"
          Broomfield, Howard. Excerpt from "In Doig Peoples Ears"
          O'Callahan, Jay. "The Cliffs of Culdurragh"
        - Seuphor, Michel., undated; 1; 00:42:15 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506564)
          Sinnge sannge, 1929
          Discours Politique, 1962
        - Lonsdale, Andy. "Ah ow Hurt!" / "Boxmusik", 1983; 1; 01:01:29; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506572)
          A special compilation for Henri Chopin. Dolby. Final performance in Sydney, 1983-07-23.
          "hostages"
          "dreaming"
          "the patient"
          "atomic disease"
          "prelude"
          "kommunion"
        - Marlow, Jack and Dana, Llys. Taliesin, undated; 1; 00:56:08; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506580)
        - Pavl, Al. Symptome 199.999, 1984-1990; 1; 00:58:04 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506598)
          de A à Z, 5'
          "Quelque Chose D'autre!", 16'
          "Motus Magnus", 4' 32"
          "abobo-esprit", 3' 54"
          "mille et un bonheurs obligatoires - voix Claire", 7'
          "mouvement", 6' 17"
          "nouveaux proverbes et petites comédies element terre, 8'
          "Dites! Vous me prenez pour un poète ou quoi?, 6'
        - Erratum Musical, 1994; 1; 00:49:06; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506606)
          "Erratum musical manifeste", 10' 40"
          "Meditation on violence", 3'
          "Souffle initiatique, 9' 30"
          "Lothar", 5' 41"
          "Guetr'", 15'
          "Somnolence métallique, 6' 10"
        - Lautpoesie, Eine Anthologie, Folge 1, 1987; 1; 00:45:50; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506614)
          Seite A / Seite B
          1. Porta, Pietro. "Incognita", 5' 33
          2a. Cena, Sergio. "Studio per Sdolcinato", 1' 37
          2b. Cena, Sergio. "Studio per Affanno", 2' 00
          2c. Cena, Sergio. "Studio per Sbellicamento, 1' 34"
          3. Papenfub, Bert. Kitt'she Sentenzen zur Selbst-Stefung & merwigem Streichtum, insamt dalled aschkenasen=farbenen Skorne-Fackeleien, 6' 01
          4. Bertola, Carla. Sirene, oh sirene, 4' 48
          1a. Vitacchio, Alberto. "Racconto cinque", 3' 25
          1b. Vitacchio, Alberto. "Remote control", 2' 22
          2a. Riha, Karl. "Lautgedicht in Silben", 0' 34
          2b. Riha, Karl. "Wozu überhaupt Kunst? In fremder Zunge, 0' 46
          2c. Brief an Ed Sommer, 2' 39"
          2d. Sprichwörter, 0' 25"
          3a. Adler, H. G., Vae victis, 1' 22
          3b. Die Pseudodemokratischen, 1' 39
          3c. Die Talmi-Primitiven, 2' 22
          4. Chopin, Henri. Troisieme mouvement: premiers pizzicati de bouche, 6' 12
        - Reviuw Parade-Interrationale. Culte de la Nature, 1986 September; 1; 01:01:18 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506622)
          Bertola, Carla. 6' 50"
          Chopin, Henri. (Sainte Phonie a Pied), 2' 48"
          Pithois, Pascal. 5'
          Yaset "Le Bel Oiseau" Komintern (Hommage au Maire de Tours); 1' 50"
          Roquin, Louis. "Le Vent" trompette solo, 3' 10"
          Metail, Michele. "Ethnopoeme" Nº 2, 2'
          Dreyfus, Charles. "Poesie en Plan", 1' 6"
          Savostine, Anna. "1975", 1' 33"
          Vacelet, Annie. "Words, Words, Words", 4' 22"
          Sud, Riki. "Cité Maraux 96", 2' 55
          Marque, Daniel. "Bestioles", 8' 21"
          Maraux, Yves. "Ruines", 30"
          Frontier, Alain. 5'
          Cahen, Jacqueline. (Chant et Synthe), 6' 40"
          Hubaut, Joel. 1' 45"
          Pavl, Al. (Decoration ou Peinture), 6' 55"
        - Reviuw Parade-Interrationale. L'Aiguille a Drecou, 1986 December; 1; 01:01:53; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506630)
          Montels, Bruno. (Canal Bernard), 4' 50"
          Chopin, Henri. (Sainte Phonie en "R" Majeur), 4' 25"
          Ensemble Vide. 2' 30"
          Dreyfus, Charles. 4' 11"
          Yaset "Story of Drecou" Nice. (Intermezzo from the Karelia Suite), 5' 26"
          Molnar, Katalin et Nagy, Paul. "Moi Drecou", 2' 47"
          Dreyfus, Charles. "Le Choix", 1' 10"
          Thomas, Martial. "La Verite", 36"
          En Voix Du Tres Saint-Pere. Exceptionnel! "Quand il L'Imite, Quand il Limite", 3' 15"
          Marque, Daniel. "Pointe Moins 20.000", 4' 5"
          Maisons, Bruno. 4' 45"
          Pavl, Al. "Symptomes 199.999"
          Je Veux Rester Normal, 1' 55"
          Animal, 1' 44"
          Avions, 4' 5"
          Document, 7' 35"
          Noir, 3' 10"
          Passager, 1' 15"
        - Reviuw Parade-Interrationale. Sheep-Boy, 1987 December; 1; 00:59:15; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506648)
          New Mixage, 7' 12"
          Yaset et Hackenboer. "Ne Jetons Pas De Perles Aux Pourceaux" (extrait), 22'
          Ensemble Vide. Leguen, Yannick. "Je Veux Dominer!", 2' 36"
          Carre, Remy. "Monomes/textes P. Guyotat", 17'
          Pavl, Al. Symptome 199.999 "Singulier", 7' 11"
      - Works by others, unsorted, (36 audiocassettes)
        - Making a tape at the Rainbow Cafe, 1981 December 18; 1; 00:20:20; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503272)
          Graffiti
          Balshazzar's Vegan Feast
        - Media-Space. Bureau-Cast, 1983 November 11; 1; Deterioration to parts of the audiocassette (sticky shed syndrome) has been found. The tape has not been digitized. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503280)
          Side A/Side B
          Fatman Overall
          Glassy
          Office
          'Ooks Like
          Folley
          Hopeless
          Satire
          Holy Cows
          Signs
          Be Nice
          Numbers
          Sexicon
          Random Mass
          Bureau
        - Dufrêne, François. Crirythmes, 1977; 1; 00:45:38 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503298)
          A note written on the audiocassette reads: For our Jean Chopin/with my best wishes/Edufre[?]. Other notes regarding the cassette include: 9,5 cm/sec; stereo; playing time: 44'10".
          1. Pour la montre, et contre (1967), 5'55"
          2. Crirythme des Cocons contractants (1967), 4'30"
          3. Stress Man (1967), 11'10"
          4. Paris-Stockholm (1972), 10'30"
          5. Crirythme en rut (1969), 12'00"
        - Bérard, Stéphane. "Tragédie, de toute façon", March 1993; 1; 00:53:16; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503306)
          Opéra. 56'. Prise de son: Pierre Suanez.
        - Minarelli, Enzo. Sinergicoral, 1982; 1; 00:59:33 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503314)
          60', stereo, Italy
          1. Sinergicoral, 3'50"
          2. Phon Poems, a (4'), b (2'15"), c (1'50")
          3. Eterne Vocali, a (3'), b (5'25")
          4. Rime in ò/ì, 2'20"
          5. Argentiadi, bread & water poems, a (1'30"), b (1'30")
          6. Cruciverbafonie, 30"
          1. Argentiadi, bread & water poems, c (3'), d (4'20")
          2. Lablingdent, 45"
          3. People, 4'
          4. Fum Poem Fum, 2'30"
          5. In Levare in Battere, 3'50"
          6. Scioglipoesie, 6'15", a, b, c, d
          Di Rimando, 3'
        - Finch, Peter. Big Band Dance Music, undated; 1; 00:20:17 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503322)
          stereo, C 25
          "Blue" (second voice - Bob Cobbing)
          "Miss Skin" (saxophone - Barry Pilcher)
          "Four Times as Many"
          "Seasonal Cycle"
        - Finch, Peter. Dances Interdites, undated; 1; 00:31:49; Program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503330)
          Stereo, 32 minutes. Side B: "Instantaneous Magnetism", available on insert only.
          "Argentina"
          "Bright Wind"
        - Andreyev, Oleg and Edwards, Ken. Where is the Line Between Us?, undated; 1; 00:19:06 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503348)
          Liner notes included with the audiocassette reads: "Teorii" or "Ink abandoned on Paper" was recorded at a private reading late 1983 in East Berlin. Oleg Andreyev born 1937 Kiev/USSR of no permanent address since 1977... "Lexical dub - for Sarah Tisdall". Ken Edwards born Gibraltar 1950 since 1968 in London. Sarah Tisdall, a junior civil servent, was sentenced to 6 months imprisonment for photocopying a memo about cruise missile deployment and disclosing it to the Guardian newspaper.
        - Mann, Chris. talking about healesville, 1984?; 1; 01:41:04; Low-level cross talk can be heard at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503355)
          A handwritten note on the inside cover of the audiocassette reads: [good day], u wanna do something in spring? being a dad is bloody busy, love n stuff.
        - Baobab, undated; 1; 00:50:16; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503363)
          Gerald Bisinger "Gespräche Gespräche Gespräche"
          Julien Blaine "W M Quinzième - 1, 2, 3", "Conversation Brasilienne 1977", "Comptes Rendus - 1, 2"
          Fulvio Abbate & Grancesco Gambara "Cotito"
          Dick Higgins "Glass Lass" (and the voices of Alison Knowles & Giulia Niccolai)
          Harry Hoogstraten "Sara Mi Na Nah - 1, 2, 3", "The Do-Dah" from "Celebrations Galore", "For the Painter's Colours" (and the voice of Susanne Hann), "Venice Already"
          Giulia Niccolai "Toti Scialoja Ballad", "Maria Theresopiel", "In the Downs"
          Adriano Spatola "Aviation Aviateur"
          F. Tiziano "Tramgedy", "To Type to Hit"
          Ivano D'Aurelio "Concerto per Stockhausen"
          Arrigo Lora-Totino "Discussione del Duemila", "Dibattito in A", "Odissea"
        - Rue, Rik. Bend An Ear, 1; 00:43:46; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503371)
          "I've Never Been This Way Before"
          "Twisted Words and Misguided Mantras"
          "Other Voices 1"
          "Lost and Rediscovered Voices"
          "Banging the Door"
          "Dub of St-retia"
          "I've Got Rhythm"
          "Dead Travel Faster"
          "Visions of Future Past"
          "Six Days of Work One of Play"
          "Scoobly Doo"
          "Three Cheers for Civilization"
        - Nitsch, Hermann. 6. Sinfonie/Teil (1 of 2), 1980 November 1; 1; 01:01:30; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099369820)
        - Nitsch, Hermann. 6. Sinfonie/Teil (2 of 2), 1980 November 1; 1; 00:55:54; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503389)
        - Chopin, Henri. 30599, undated; 1; 00:56:33 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503397)
        - F.C.R. de Faz, 1992 May 31; 1; 00:22:51 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503405)
        - Gurdjieff, George and De Hartmann, Thomas. Piano, undated; 1; 01:14:58; Static can be heard on the tape. Clicks and pops can be heard as well. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503413)
        - The Listening Room. Chopin, Staccati, 1991-1992?; 1; 00:27:01; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503421)
        - Sous le figuier le bonheur, 2000 August 2; 1; 00:25:12 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503439)
        - Chopin, Henri. Émission ans, 1988?; 1; 00:38:20; Static and a high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503447)
          bonjour voici a peliti, émission A.B.C., à bienlol, [kaye] [meilez]
        - Keppler. Chopin musik/poetry manifesto, 1985 April; 1; 00:07:55 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503454)
        - Gaburo, Kenneth. Few <Creation>, 1985 April 9; 1; 00:05:21 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503462)
          Gaburo/Chopin (Voices); 2-track, 5'29"; Iowa Experimental Studio
        - Motessori, Joachim. Les Concrétions - La question oubliée/Cellule Erratumique, 1995 August, 1996 January; 1; 01:06:15; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503470)
        - Festival Poésie, 1992; 1; 00:36:02; Static can be heard on the tape. Audio on the left channel is silent for the first 17 seconds of the program and again from 00:28-21:05. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503488)
        - Schipper, Elke. Parole, undated; 1; 00:31:13 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503496)
          List of contents on the cassette:
          1. Perpetual Motion
          2. Me Not Me
          3. Zentrifuge
          4. Frequenzgang
          Chaine Parleé
          6. Per a la Teresa I
          7. Collegno Colerico
        - Kostelanetz, Richard. Foreshortenings & Other Stories, 1976; 1; 00:48:33; A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503504)
        - F. C. R. de Faz, 1992 May 31; 1; 01:37:14; This audiocassette may be a duplicate. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503512)
        - Les Dossiers D'Espace 2: Poesie Sonore, 1992 March 30; 1; 00:58:10; A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503520)
        - Chopin, Henri. Fresque de L'Impalpable voix, 1993; 1; 00:19:17 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503538)
        - Conference S.A.B.N. of Henri Chopin, undated; 1; 00:45:38; The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503546)
          le 28 of 93
        - Cobbing, Bob. BBC, 1983?; 1; 00:42:40 (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503553)
        - Hörfunkbeiträge "Festival der Internationalen Lautpoesie", 1992 October 29 to 1992 November 7; 1; 00:32:17; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503561)
          Radio-Beiträge
          1. WDR 5, Radio für Südwestfalen, 1992-10-29
          2. SFB Berlin, Magazin Klassik plus, 1992-11-02
          3. WDR 2, Magazin Echo West, 1992-10-30
          4. WDR 1, Magazin Forum West, 1992-10-31
          5. Radio Siegen, Lautpoesie-Parodie "Neues von Friseur Birkelbach", 1992-11-05 and 1992-11-07
        - PAB Emission, 1979 December 20; 1; 01:02:37; Static and high frequency noise can be heard on the program. The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503579)
          Daive
        - Thomas, Martin and Swivel, Mark. Sidevalving: A Theory of Modern Prisons, undated; 1; 01:17:58; Static can be heard on the tape. High background noise can be heard as well. The audio is silent from 26:15-31:07. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503587)
          Documentary on imprisonment in Queensland.
        - Chopin, Henri. T to 7, undated; 1; 00:46:48; A high amount of buzz can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503595)
        - Schwerner, Armand and Economou, George. 92 St Poetry Center, 1972 May 1; 1; 01:07:38; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503603)
        - Chopin, Henri. Emission WDR, 1983 November; 1; 00:56:46; The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002104503611)
          Das Alto Europas ouvs dem Ursprung des Sprachen; 56'40", stereo
      - Works by others, unsorted, (34 audiocassettes)
        - Fontana, Giovanni. "Antologia Sonora", undated; 1; 00:47:49 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506655)
          "Maschera mitopoietica", 1981, 2' 15"
          "Traccia pensieri", 1976, 3' 16"
          "SOS", 1980, 1' 25"
          "Cancellature", 1977, 2' 18"
          Utricolo / Sacculo (da "Radio / Dramma"), 1981, 1' 44"
          "Alalìa", 1983/85, 3' 59"
          "Petites poupées", 1970, 1' 59"
          "Poema strumentale", 1969, 4' 18"
          "Sirene", 1980, 1' 44"
          Silenzio di sciagura (da "Radio/Dramma", 1979, 1' 44"
          "Tarocco meccanico", 1973/74, 3' 51"
          Audiocollage (da "radiopoema"), 1968, 2' 05"
          "Poema Larsen" (Feedback poem), 1983/88, 8' 10"
          Scansioni (dallo spettacolo teatrale "Sturizia"), 1971, 3' 15"
          La gai morte, 1973, 2' 35"
        - Hammersley, Richard. "sed / did / diction" / "t wn s 002", 1980; 1; 01:02:27; The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506663)
        - Adamczewska, Joanna and Wilmanski, Tomasz. "Acoustic Books" / "Mur-L'amour", Dzwieki, 1991 January -1993 June; 1; 00:40:03; Audio on the left channel is recorded at a lower volume. Audio is muffled from about 20:00 until the end of the tape. There is a high amount of hiss on the tape. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506671)
        - Heidsieck, Bernard. Poésie Sonore, "Canal Street", 1985; 1; 00:57:19 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506705)
          Contents on the audiocassette include: Face A: poème-partition sur les lettres O et E, Canal Street Nº 12, 15, 16; Face B: Canal Street Nº 17, 18, 22, 26, 28, 29, 31, 32, 34, 35.
        - Hudak, John. The Clockmaker, 1989 September; 1; 01:02:25 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506697)
          "Temperance"
          "Noumenal Change"
        - Polipoesia Primera Antologia, undated; 1; 01:04:59; A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506689)
        - Side Car, undated; 1; 00:00:41 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506713)
          Taliesin. Hautension
          Llys Dana: Alkaest.
        - NMA 5, undated; 1; 00:58:33; A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506721)
        - Crissements Sous La Roue Du Temps, 1985; 1; 00:19:13 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506747)
        - Bouche, Thierry. L'information du jour, 1988-1989; 1; 00:59:45 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506754)
          1. Salut à toi, Nancarrow, 3' 26"
          2. Jubilée, 7'
          3. Tout Electre, 2' 35"
          4. J'y croix ?, 4' 55"
          5. Le temps qu'il fait, 6' 55"
          6. L'état, 3' 30"
          1. Vers le noir, 5' 50"
          2. Coucou, Purcell, 3' 45"
          3. La bouche, 5' 15"
          4. Profanations/Permutations, 11' 45"
          5. Novi Sad, 3' 30"
        - Hammersley, Richard. "Lobby Newsletter 16", 1981; 1; 00:22:32; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506739)
          essential style
          ae wake
          interview - Richard Hammersley to yz
        - Gaburo "Antiphony VIII", undated; 1; 00:16:29 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506762)
          (Révolution) percussion: Steve Schiele
        - Dreyfus, Charles and Papp, Tibor. Le Trou Noir 84, undated; 1; 01:04:49; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506770)
        - Polkinhorn, Harry., undated; 1; 00:30:06 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506788)
          1. Wer
          2. Water
          3. Man
          4. Wind
          5. Pneu
          6. Speak
        - Nitnelav, Tumla. Trout 1-5 / ...11, undated; 1; 00:28:23; Program distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506796)
        - Scherstjanoi, Valeri. Polyphonia, 1991; 1; 00:34:16 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506804)
        - Heidsieck, Bernard. Poésie Sonore, "Canal Street", 1985; 1; 00:57:16; The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506812)
          This appears to be a duplicate.
        - Le livre sonore / Le sonosaure, 1987; 1; 01:26:47; The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506820)
          Kinkao (14' 22")
          Petites orgues (7' 28")
          Tribal (7' 28")
          Queiques formules utiles (6' 34")
          Ad-delà des macines (7' 14")
          S'abolir sonore (14' 30")
          Rire construit (4' 50")
        - Pastior, Oskar. Der Krimgotische Fächer, 1978, 1979; 1; 00:54:12 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506846)
        - Beckett, Samuel. Poémes suivi de Mirlitonnades / Imagination Morte Imaginez Bing, 1984; 1; 00:34:59 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506853)
        - Hudak, John., undated; 1; 01:02:39 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506861)
          "Clarity"
          "Pleasantly with Me"
        - Higgins, Dick. Sound Poetry, undated; 1; 00:31:14 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506879)
        - Tardos, Anne. New Wilderness Audiographics, "Gatherings", 1981; 1; 00:51:49 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506887)
          There is a handwritten message included with the audiocassette. It reads: For the great Chopin with best wishes and friendship, Anne Tardos, Stockholm 1984-04-15
          "Refrigerator Defrosting", 1975, 14' 7"
          "Seven-Layer Song", 1980, 4'
          "Voices from Video", 1980-81, 5' 5"
          "Pipes at 110 Mercer, November 1974", 13' 30"
          "Real Sleeper, Real Dreamer", 1976, 9' 52"
        - Hammersley, Richard. "Lobby Newsletter 16", 1981; 1; 00:22:22; The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506895)
          This audiocassette appears to be a duplicate.
        - Reviuw Parade-Interrationale. La Pote Au Japon!, 1987 September; 1; 00:57:13; The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506903)
        - Wendt, Larry. "The Remembrance of a Technological Past", undated; 1; 01:03:01 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506911)
          "Where I Am From"
          "The South Bay Homebrew Inventors Club"
          "Muffie"
          "Toad Farming For Profit"
          "Silicon Valley Ghost Town"
          "The Great Silicon Valley Toad Plague"
          "Gene Cot Toad"
          "Silicon Valley Horror Story"
          "Silicon Valley Love Story"
          "The End of San Jose"
        - Schwerner, Armand. New Wilderness Audiographics, 1977; 1; 00:56:19 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506929)
          "the triumph of the will"
          "Tablets 15-19"
          "the work"
          "Bacchae Sonnets"
          "the joy of Sven Hedin"
          "Bar Mitzvah for Adam"
        - Vizents, A. Furniture, 1982 June 7; 1; 00:15:17 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506937)
          "Wood Chair"
          "Couch"
          "Upholstered Chair"
          "Wardrobe"
          "Venetian Blind"
        - Bertozzi, Gabriela-Aldo. La Signora Proteo, 1993; 1; 00:09:15 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506945)
          Bertozzi, G-A. "Ouverture"
          Mattioli, G. "Monologo finale"
        - Kagel, Mauricio. (Hörspiel) Ein Aufnahmezustand / Der Tribun, undated; 1; 01:37:37; The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506952)
        - "La Nouvelle Revue D'Art Moderne", 1980 January; 1; 01:19:07; Audio levels vary from 35:36-39:30. The left channel of audio is silent from 1:13:02-1:15:03. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506960)
        - Curtay, Jean-Paul. Body Music 1, 1980; 1; 01:23:04; The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506838)
          Cage, John. Introduction to Jean-Paul Curtay's performance
          What is Body Music?
          Teasing Release (7' 56")
          Abirdment (18' 54")
          Anatomy of the bodily sound (15' 19")
        - Media-Space, 1982 July 6; 1; 00:31:24 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506978)
          "So No No"
          "Worker Worble"
          "Factual Physical"
          "March Fly"
          "Mediation"
          "Double Double"
          "Driving Around"
          "Coming and Going"
        - Media-Space, 1982 August 12; 1; 00:25:45 (Box 69, Item barcode 39002104506986)
          Thomas, Paul. "Simulcast"
          Vizents, A. "Get Me"
          Thomas, Paul. "Think Nothing of It"
          Vizents, A. "Scratching"
      - Works by others, unsorted, (34 audiocassettes)
        - Chopin, Henri., 1983; 1; 00:50:28; The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507463)
        - Maillard, Claude. "La Contadora", 1984; 1; 00:45:46 (Box 70, Item barcode 39002104507471)